&gt;&gt; Good afternoon everybody.
&gt;&gt; 大家下午好
Hello to everybody who's still
谢谢你们
here.
今天来到这里
I'm Steve Hayman.
我叫 Steve Hayman
I'm a consulting engineer from
我是一名顾问工程师
Toronto, Canada.
来自加拿大多伦多
Any Canadians here?
在坐的有加拿大人吗
Good. How's it going, eh?
好的 大家好啊
I'd like to say hello to those
我想向你们问好
of you who are still here late
现在是周五下午
on Friday afternoon.
而你们依旧在这里
And to everyone who's watching
我也要向日后
the video in the future, hello
观看视频的人问好
people in the future with the
他们可能生活在
flying cars and everything.
有飞行汽车等高科技的未来
I'm very excited to see what
我非常激动想知道
that turns out to be.
未来会变成什么样
But today we have the thrilling
而今天我们的话题也同样令人激动
topic of iOS Configuration and
它就是
APIs for Kiosk and Assessment
自助服务与评价测试 App 的
Apps.
iOS 配置与 API
What are we talking about?
具体来说是什么
We're talking about locking an
我们讨论的是
iPad to a single application.
将 iPad 锁定在某一特定的应用上
We're going to talk about
我们将介绍
different ways that you might do
你可以完成此项功能的
that.
不同方法
Some of them are manual
有一些需要
processes.
手动处理
Some of them are programmatic.
有一些则是程序化的
But let me show you a couple of
关于刚刚说到的内容
examples of what we're talking
让我来向你们展示
about right now.
一些例子
So here's my iPad.
这是我的 iPad
Here's one thing you can do.
你可以这么做
Anybody can do this on any iPad.
所有人都可以在任何 iPad 上这么做
Anybody can go to Settings,
任何人都可以前往“设置”>
General, Accessibility, way down
“通用”>“辅助功能”
at bottom, Guided Access.
然后滑到最下方的“引导式访问”
And if you turn this on, it is
如果你开启此功能
now possible to lock an iPad,
现在你能够锁住 iPad
any iPad, to any arbitrary
将任意 iPad
application.
锁在任意的应用上
A lot of parents and teachers do
很多家长和老师
this before they turn over their
在把 iPad 交给孩子之前
iPad to their child.
都会这么做
For instance, if your child was
比如说 如果你的孩子
very interested in maps, you
对地图非常感兴趣
could launch Maps, and then
你可以启动“地图”
since Guided Access is on, you
因为开启了引导式访问
can triple tap, one, two, three
你可以点击
times, on the Home button, and
三次 Home 键 1 2 3
supply a pass code.
并提供一个密码
A very secret pass code.
密码要设计的
No guessing.
很难猜
[sound effects].
音效
And now I can hand the iPad to
现在我就可以把 iPad
my geography-obsessed child, and
交给我对地理着迷的孩子
they can play with Maps all day
他们一整天都可以使用“地图”
long, but they can't touch the
但他们无法使用
Home button.
Home 键
They can't get out and start
他们不能退出应用
messing with my stuff, until I
弄乱我的东西
triple tap the Home button
直到我再次点击三次
again, one, two, three, and put
Home 键 1 2 3
in the pass code.
并输入密码
So this is Guided Access.
这就是“引导式访问”
This is an accessibility
这是 Apple 的一个辅助技术
technology from Apple that's
很久之前
been around for a long time.
就已经有了
It's a basic way to lock an iPad
这是将 iPad
to any application that you
锁在你想要的应用上的
want.
基本方法
That's one way, but I want to
这是一个办法
show you another way.
但我想向你们展示另一种方法
We're all developers.
我们都是开发人员
Let's talk about a programmatic
让我们来说一说
way to do this.
完成该功能的程序性方法
I have a testing application on
在这里我有一个提供考试的应用
here that you might see in a
你可能在学校
school for administering
进行标准化考试的时候
standardized tests.
见过它
And in schools, we are a little
在学校
bit concerned about letting
我们都非常担心
students touch the Home button,
在考试途中
and fire up Safari, and go to
学生会点击 Home 键
Wikipedia during the test.
使用 Safari 打开 Wikipedia
We don't really want that
我们真的不希望
happening.
这种事情发生
So an application like this one,
因此一个像这样的应用
when I tap Start Test, we're not
当我打开它的时候
locked right at the moment.
我们并没有马上被锁定
I can still hit the Home button.
我还可以点击 Home 键
But once I touch Start Test,
但我一旦点击 Start Test
this particular app is set up to
这个 App 就会在我点击的时候
lock iOS on demand, at the
按照需求锁住 iOS
moment I touch that button.
我点击的时候
You get a little panel here that
这里会出现一个小面板
says, "Do you want to confirm
显示着“你是否确定让
app self lock?"
App 自锁？”
And if I say yes, the test
如果我选择“是”
begins.
考试就开始了
The Home button is now locked.
现在 Home 键已经被锁住
It was locked by some code that
这个锁定是通过代码实现的
I'll show you at exactly this
之后我会给大家
point.
展示代码
And I can't cheat in the test.
我在考试中不能作弊
I can't hit the Home button to
我不能通过点击 Home 键
get out.
退到主屏幕
I can submit my answer here,
我可以在这里提交我的答案
Ottawa.
是“渥太华”
And at the moment I hit Submit,
我点击“提交”的时候
this particular app unlocks iOS.
这个 App 又会解锁 iOS
So there's a function we're
我们将要介绍这个功能
going to tell you about that
如何实现
turns the locking on and off.
锁定和解锁
So now I'm back to a point where
现在我又能够
I can hit the Home button.
点击 Home 键了
So those are two different
有两种不同的方法
approaches.
锁住 Home 键
One of them a fairly manual
一种是完全手动的
approach, Guided Access, walking
通过“引导式访问”
around and actually triple
并在设备上
tapping on a device.
点击三次 Home 键
And then the other one is a
另一个是
programmatic approach, which I
程序的方法
think you would agree is a
相信你也同意
little more flexible.
后者较为灵活
Those are two ways.
这是两种方法
I'm going to talk about four
我将介绍
ways that you might lock an
锁定应用的
application.
四种方法
One that we just saw was Guided
一个是我们刚刚看到的
Access.
“引导式访问”
This is a great technology for
这是一个很好的技术
keeping a child, for instance,
可以让孩子
focused on a certain task.
专心于一项特定的任务
You can lock your child into
比如说你可以把你的孩子锁定在
Swift Playgrounds and not let
Swift Playgrounds 中
them out until they can explain
直到他们能够解释
the difference between a struct
结构和类的区别
and a class, for instance.
再解锁
Whatever scenario you want, you
不管在哪种情形下
can lock a child to a particular
你都能把孩子
application.
锁定在特定的应用中
There's another technology
在自助服务中
you'll often see in Kiosks,
你将经常看到另一种技术
single app mode.
就是单一 App 模式
This is useful to keep the iPad
它可以有效的将 iPad
pretty much permanently locked
几乎永久的
to a particular application.
锁在某个特定的应用上
You've probably seen this if
如果你去过 Apple 商店的话
you've gone to an Apple store.
你可能见过这样的情况
There's some iPads on display
用于展示的一些 iPad
that are permanently running an
永远在运行
information application, and you
信息介绍的应用
can't get out.
你无法退出
But there are two techniques
但编程人员还可以使用
available to programmers.
另外两个技术
The first is called autonomous
第一个叫
single app mode.
自主单一 App 模式
Picture a situation where you
想想这样一个场景
have a medical clinic, and the
你有一个医疗诊所
nurse is using an application
护士正在使用一款
with confidential information on
含有保密信息的应用
it, and then a patient arrives.
然后来了一名患者
You'd like to hand them the iPad
你希望将 iPad 交给患者
to check in and have it locked
完成登记
during that little transaction
并在此期间锁住 iPad
and have it unlocked when you
拿回 iPad 时
get it back so that they can't
再解锁
hit the Home button and mess
这样患者就不会
around during one section of
在你 App 的运行过程中
your application.
点击 Home 键随意使用了
That's called autonomous single
这就叫
app mode.
自主单一 App 模式
It's a single app mode where
进行锁定时
locking takes place, but it's
它是单一 App 模式
autonomous, because it's your
但它是自主的
application that decides when
你的应用将自行决定
the right time is.
何时进行锁定
And there's a fourth mode
第四种模式是
specifically designed for the
特别为那些
education community for people
教育界
building standardized test
创建标准化考试应用的人
applications, automatic
设计的
assessment configuration.
叫做自主评价配置
This is for students taking a
用于参加重大考试的学生
high stakes test, and it locks
它会锁定 iPad
the iPad, but it also disables
同时禁用一些
some additional features, like
附加功能
spellchecking, and auto correct,
比如拼写检查 自动更正和 Siri
and Siri that you would not want
你不会希望学生
a student to be using on a test.
在考试时使用这些功能
We're going to talk about these
我们将介绍
four scenarios.
这四个情景
They each have different
他们都有不同的
technical requirements.
技术要求
Guided Access really just works
“引导式访问”
on any iPad at all.
可以在任何 iPad 上使用
Anybody can walk up, and turn it
任何人可以拿过 iPad 开启“引导式访问”
on, and triple tap to enable it.
然后点击三次 Home 键启用它
It's a very widely available
这是一项被
technology.
广泛使用的技术
Single app mode that you would
单一 App 模式
see with Kiosks, this is
可见于自助服务中
something that only works on a
它只能在
managed and supervised device.
被管理和监控的设备上工作
So it won't work on the
它不会在普通设备上工作
run-of-the-mill, bring your own
比如你自己
iPad from home.
从家里带的 iPad
It works only on a managed
它只在被管理的设备上工作
device, and it requires support
并且需要 MDM
from MDM and from the system
和系统管理员
administrator.
的支持
Somebody has to designate
需要有人指定
exactly which apps, exactly
现在要锁定
which single app, we're going to
哪些
lock right now.
或哪个特定的 App
Autonomous single app mode, much
自主单一 App 模式
more flexible.
要灵活的多
It still requires supervised
它仍然需要被监控的设备
devices, and it requires the
并且需要管理员
administrator to white list
为特定的应用设置白名单
specific applications, but now
但现在它意味着
it means that the iPad can
iPad 可以
decide.
自主决定
Your app can decide when to turn
你的 App 可以决定
the locking on and when to turn
何时锁定
it off.
何时解锁
And finally, the last one,
最终的最后一个是
automatic assessment
自主评价配置
configuration, is the best for
它是评价系统开发人员的
assessment developers because it
最佳选择
locks the iPad and it also
因为它不仅能够锁定 iPad
disables a whole variety of
还能禁用一系列功能
features that creative students
充满“创造力”的学生
might use to enhance their ways
可能在考试中使用这些功能
to answer questions on a test.
帮助自己回答问题
That automatic assessment
这个自主评价配置
configuration requires a special
需要向 Apple 申请
entitlement that you can apply
特殊授权
from Apple, but once you've got
一旦你获得授权
that entitlement, your app can
你的 App 就可以
lock any device, whether it's
锁定任何设备
managed or not.
无论该设备是否被管理
So locking an iPad
所以实现程序化的
programmatically.
锁定 iPad
Several different ways.
有几个不同的方法
Guided access, we saw a moment
我们刚刚见到的
ago, is a great way to focus a
“引导式访问”
child on a particular task, and
是让孩子专注特定任务的好方法
it has some obvious advantages.
它的优势很明显
Anybody can set it up.
任何人都可以设置
It's very easy to set up.
设置起来也很容易
And a couple of concerns.
但也有一些不便
It's not a particularly scalable
但它不具有可扩展性
way to do anything, because you
因为你必须
have to walk around and actually
走上前去
touch every iPad.
点击每一台 iPad
If you have hundreds of students
如果你有成百名学生
who are about to take a test,
他们将要进行考试
someone would have to walk
那要有人走过去
around and touch the Home button
在这上百个设备
three times on each of the 100
每一个的 Home 键上
devices.
点击三次
That doesn't scale very well,
这并不能规模化操作
plus you have to manage a pass
外加你还要
code.
管理密码
So it's great for some
因此它在某些情况下适用
situations, but not others.
其他情况就不合适了
Single app mode that you might
你可以对 kiosk
do with a kiosk brings a level
使用单一 App 模式
of remote control to this
从而获得一定程度的
process.
远程控制
If you have iPads where there's
如果你有一些 iPad
only one application that you
你只想让它们
might ever want to run, maybe
运行一个应用
something that displays train
比如显示火车时刻
schedules or conference room
或预订会议室
reservations, an admin can push
管理员可以向
a command to a managed iPad to
被管理的 iPad 推送一条命令
lock it right now to that
将它锁定在
application.
该应用上
In fact, you can lock hundreds
事实上
or thousands of applications of
你可以同时锁定
iPads simultaneously.
成百上千台 iPad
Here's what it might look like.
举个具体的例子
Let's suppose you have some sort
假设你有一个
of a tourism kiosk, and you want
旅游类自助服务应用
your iPad to run this
你希望你的 iPad
application only.
仅运行这个应用
An administrator using an MDM
管理员会运行 MDM 工具
tool, which specify that your
指明你的应用
application is the one that's
是单个 App 模式中
allowed to do single app mode,
唯一被允许运行的应用
and then the moment they push
在推送这个配置的时候
this configuration out, the iPad
iPad 就会立即
immediately launches that app,
启动该 App
and it stays in that app.
并留在该 App 内
If you reboot the device, it
如果你重启该设备
goes back to the kiosk
它也会再次回到
application again.
自助服务应用
This is a good way to pretty
这是一个很好的方法
much permanently lock an iPad to
能够尽量永久的将 iPad
a particular application.
锁在一个特定的应用上
The way you get out of this is
退出该模式的方法是
to push a new command from the
从管理控制台
Admin Console to remove this
推送一条新命令
single app mode setting.
移除单一 App 模式的设置
Very useful to lock thousands of
对同时锁定成千上万台设备
devices simultaneously and more
非常有用
or less permanently, but it does
并且可以几乎永久锁定
require IT involvement.
只是需要 IT 人员的介入
We have seen situations where
我们遇到过一些情况
people have forgotten to unlock
有人忘记通过该技术
the iPads via this technology.
解锁 iPad
If you were a school, and you
如果你在学校
locked all the iPads to the math
将所有的 iPad 都锁定为数学考试
test, and you forgot to unlock
并且忘记解锁它们
them, now nobody can do anything
那所有人都用不了 iPad 了
until you remember to push out
直到你想起
that next command.
推送下一条命令
It does require a supervised
该技术需要使用通过 MDM 管理的
device managed by MDM, and I
受监控设备
would say the main downside to
我要说这个技术最大的不足就是
this is that developers really
开发人员没有
have no control.
控制的权限
When you lock with single app
一旦设置为单一 App 模式
mode, the device immediately
设备就会立即锁定
locks, we're stuck in that
我们就被卡在
application.
该应用里
Not very [inaudible].
而不是逐步锁定
Wouldn't it be interesting if --
如果作为开发人员
wouldn't it be great if, as a
你可以控制什么时候
developer, you could control
进行锁定
exactly when that locking
难道不是更好
happened?
更有趣吗
Like, for instance, if you had a
就像比如说
medical practice like this, with
你有一个这样的医疗机构
a patient management application
和一个充满保密信息的
full of confidential
患者管理应用
information, when the patient
当患者到来的时候
arrives, wouldn't it be great if
如果你可以把
you could hand them the iPad,
iPad 交给他们
touch that button, and know that
点击一个按钮
the iPad is locked, the Home
知道 iPad 已经被锁定
button does not work while we
在这个界面无法使用 Home 键
are on this screen.
这难道不是很方便吗？
And then once the patient fills
一旦患者填写了
in all their information, they
所有的个人信息
might touch Check In, hand the
他们就可以点击“登记”
iPad back to me, and now it
然后将 iPad 交还给我们
could be unlocked, and we would
此时 iPad 会解锁
regain full control.
我们又可以重新控制了
Wouldn't it be great if clicking
如果点击
that button right there, right
这个按钮
clicking that button right there
就可以开启锁定
turned locking on?
难道不是很棒吗？
&gt;&gt; Yeah!
&gt;&gt; 哇
&gt;&gt; Yes, yes, you're right.
&gt;&gt; 是的 是的 你们是对的
It would be great.
这确实很棒
Wouldn't that be great?
不是吗
What about this side?
这边呢
This side, you think that would
这边的听众
be great?
你们觉得呢
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
&gt;&gt; 是的
&gt;&gt; Yeah, it would be kind of
&gt;&gt; 是的 这会很酷
cool, wouldn't it?
不是吗
Well, you know what, have we got
嗯 你们猜
a function for you.
我们有没有提供这个功能
Well, as a matter of fact, that
嗯 事实上
would be great, and we do have a
我们确实为你们
function for you.
提供了这项功能
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
And here it is.
它就是
UIAccessibilityRequest
UIAccessibilityRequestGuidedAccessSession()
Nice, easy-to-remember function.
很好 这个函数非常好记
That turns locking on and off.
它控制锁定和解锁
Here's another function.
还有另一个函数
Is Guided Access Enabled?
叫 UIAccessibilityIsGUidedAccessEnabled()
It's a Boolean.
这是一个布尔型函数
Is it on or off?
你可以用它
You can check.
检查现在是锁定还是解锁的状态
And there's a notification
这是你们一直想要的
you've asked for.
通知函数
You can be alerted when the
当锁定状态更改时
status changes.
你会收到提醒
But mostly, there's this
但最主要的
function here,
是这个函数
UIAccessibilityRequest
UIAccessibilityRequestGuidedAccessSession()
This is the key.
它是关键
If your device and your
如果你的设备
application are set up the right
和应用进行了正确的设置
way, and there is some setup
并且完成了所需的安装
required, then your app can call
你的 App 就可以
this function lock the iPad
调用该函数立即锁定 iPad
right now, and it can call it
并且通过再次调用
again to unlock.
进行解锁
And let me underline that.
让我强调一下
If the iPad and your application
只有当 iPad 和你的应用
are set up the right way, this
进行了正确的设置才可以
is a powerful function that is
这是一个非常强大的函数
not available to all
不是所有的应用
applications.
都可以使用
Adding the code is important,
添加代码非常重要
but there's some other steps you
但你实际上还需要
actually have to do.
完成其他几个步骤
So speaking of code, let's see
既然说到了代码
some code.
就让我们看一下几段代码
You would call this function to
你需要调用该函数
start a locking session.
开始一个锁定会话
You would pass it either true or
你可以给函数传值
false.
true 或者 false
Do you want to lock?
分别代表
Do you want to unlock?
锁定和解锁
And you would also give it a
你还需要
completion handler that would be
在函数中添加完成处理器
called when your request
它会在请求完成时
completes.
被调用
It can take a second or two for
锁定或解锁可能需要一两秒
the locking to take effect, so
才会生效
you pass a completion handler,
所以你需要传入一个完成处理器
and your completion handler gets
它会获得
a Boolean parameter that
一个布尔型参数
indicates whether the request
代表请求是否
succeeded or not.
已经成功完成
It's possible that the request
有可能
could fail, and so you want to
请求会失败
actually check that.
所以你需要进行检查
But if all goes well, you can
如果一切顺利
check if the request succeed and
你也确认请求成功执行
now do something with the
那就有理由相信
confidence that the iPad is
现在 iPad 已经上锁
locked at this point, and the
Home 键无法使用
Home button is disabled.
你就可以进行想要的下一步操作了
So in our hypothetical medical
在我们假想的医疗机构的例子中
example, let's suppose we have a
让我们假设我们已经有了
function like this that loads
这样一个函数
New View Controller with a
它能够启动新视图控制器
patient check-in screen on in.
显示患者登记的界面
you could wrap that in code like
你可以像这样把它放进代码中
this, and then that transition
那么只有当设备被成功
would only happen if the device
锁定时
had been locked successfully.
才会发生跳转
Then when the patient is done,
当患者完成操作时
you've got some other function
你需要执行另一个函数
that transitions back to the
从而回到主界面
main screen, you would put
你可以把类似这样的函数
something like this in here.
放在这里
You would say
你可以设置
UIAccessibilityRequest
UIAccessibilityRequestGuidedAccessSession()
GuidedAccessSession false, and
的参数为 false
that's a request to turn off at
这就是关闭
app lock at that point.
App 锁定的请求
There's another one you can
你还可以调用
call.
另一个函数
Is Guided Access enabled, true
UIAccessibilityIsGuidedAccessEnabled()
or false?
通过返回值是 true 还是 false
You can do some extra checks.
做一些额外的检查
You can check at any time
你可以随时检查
whether you're currently in a
现在是否处于
locked state or not.
锁定的状态
There's also a notification,
这里还有一个通知函数
UIAccessibilityRequest
UIAccessibilityRequestGuidedAccessStatusDidChange()
GuidedAccessStatusDidChange, and
你可以使用它
you can register for this, and
这样一来
your app can be notified
当锁定状态发生更改
anywhere as the status turns on
无论是开启还是关闭
and off.
你的 App 都能立刻收到通知
So all this technology taken
所以将所有这些技术
together is called autonomous
结合起来
single app mode, ASAM.
就是自主单一 App 模式 ASAM
It's like single app mode, but
它与单一 App 模式类似
it's autonomous, because your
但它是自主的
app can control exactly when the
因为你的 App 可以控制
locking and unlocking takes
何时
place.
锁定与解锁
You can lock just part of an
你可以锁定
application.
应用的一部分
Now for this to work, iPads do
为了实现这一功能
need to be set up in a
iPad 需要进行
particular way.
特定的设置
Let's talk about the
让我们讨论一下
requirements.
这些需要满足的要求
The first requirement, you have
第一个要求
to write the code.
你必须编写代码
You have to call that function.
必须调用该函数
Second requirement, the devices
第二个要求
have to be supervised, which is
所用设备必须是受监控的
a sort of extreme form of iOS
这是一种 iOS 管理的
management.
极端形式
And thirdly, your app needs to
第三
be white listed by the MDM
你的 App 必须被 MDM 管理员
administrator.
设置为白名单
The administrator can grant
管理员必须授予
permission to call this function
特定应用
only to certain applications.
调用该函数的权限
So here's what an admin would
这就是管理员的
do.
责任
In an MDM tool, there's a place
在 MDM 工具中
where you can mark which
你可以在这里标记
applications are allowed to
允许进入和退出单一 App 模式的
enter and exit single app mode.
应用
Only the applications on this
只有名单上的应用
list will allow that function to
才被允许
work.
使用该函数
So you'd list exactly which apps
所以你需要将允许使用函数的
are allowed to use it here.
App 列在这里
And remember, this only works on
请记住
supervised iPads, not iPads that
它只能在受监控的 iPad 上工作
people are bringing from home.
不能在大家从家中带来的 iPad 上工作
Ultimately, this converts to a
最终 它将转为
particular key and value in a
配置文件中
configuration profile.
特定的 Key 和值
The bundle IDs of all the apps
所有被授权进行此项操作的 App
that are authorized to do this,
它们的数据包 ID
that's transmitted to the
将被传送到
device.
设备
And once that configuration is
一旦完成配置
set up, your app can actually
你的 App 就可以
call that function and turn the
调用该函数
locking on and off, and you have
进行锁定和解锁
control.
你也就可以进行控制了
It's autonomous single app mode.
这就是自主单一 App 模式
You can prevent people from
你可以防止人们
accidentally getting or
有意或无意的
deliberately getting out of the
退出
application.
应用
However, there are a couple of
然而它还有
issues.
一些问题
It does require an MDM managed
它需要受 MDM
and supervised device, and the
管理和监控的设备
IT department has to
并且 IT 部门需要将
specifically white list your
你的 App 加进名单
application, grant it
给 App
permission.
授权
And all this is really onerous
在某些情况下
in some situations.
实现这些操作非常繁琐
It's ideal for the patient
但对于患者登记的情景
check-in scenario or the
或者
scenario with the bank where the
银行的抵押贷款专员
mortgage specialist is handing
将 iPad 递给你
you the iPad to fill in your
填写个人信息的情景
information.
该技术则非常理想
We want to lock it right then.
我们希望 iPad 立即锁定
It's great for that kind of
它对于这些场景非常合适
scenario, but it's not really
但是对于考试评估来说
robust enough for assessment,
该技术不具有足够的
for testing.
鲁棒性或者稳健性
Testing has its own set of
考试有其自己的
requirements.
一套要求
If you're delivering a test to a
如果你在为
large group of students, it's a
一大群学生进行
kind of a high-stakes scenario.
一场重大的考试
Not only are the students going
不仅是学生们
to be judged on their knowledge,
会被依照他们的知识进行评价
but the teacher and the school
老师和学校
are going to be judged on the
也会被根据考试结果
results as well.
进行评估
So it's important that we
因此在应用中提供
deliver a test in an application
提供一场
with the highest possible
尽可能公正的考试
integrity.
就十分重要了
We don't want students cheating.
我们不希望学生作弊
That's what we're talking about
这就是我们讨论的
here.
原因
We want to make it hard for
我们希望让
students to cheat.
学生作弊变得异常困难
These three technologies are
适用于其他情景的
useful in other scenarios, but
三个技术
not in an assessment scenario,
在考试评估场景中并不适用了
because they leave certain
因为它们不能关闭
features running, like
特定功能
spellchecking and then the
比如拼写检查
dictionary lookups and so.
词典查找等等
Those are still running in these
这些功能在
other scenarios, and you
其他场景中仍然运行
wouldn't want that in a test.
但你不希望它们在考试中可用
So Apple recommends automatic
所以 Apple 推荐
assessment configuration as the
自主评价配置
method that a test builder
这是考试创建者
should adopt.
可以采用的方法
What is it?
那么它到底是什么
Well, assessment apps have
评价考试 App 会面临
unique challenges.
独特的挑战
That are a whole lot of very
iPad 上有许多非常有用的功能
useful features on iPad that are
但在进行考试时
not appropriate when a test is
不应该
actually running.
使用它们
In order to protect the
为了保证
integrity of the test, we're
考试的公平性
going to want to disable things
我们想要禁用
like copying and pasting from
从考试外复制粘贴
outside the test into the test.
进考试的功能
We're going to want to disable,
当然我们也想要
obviously, other applications.
禁用其他应用
But we're also going to want to
并且我们也想在英语考试中
disable spellchecking on an
禁用拼写检查
English test, and we're going to
并且禁用
want to disable the built-in
内置
dictionary.
词典
So you need to be able to
所以你需要禁用
disable certain hardware
特定的硬件功能
features to run a secure test,
以进行严格的考试
and you might not have
虽然你可能还没想到
considered this, but you also
但你肯定也需要
need to disable sharing off the
禁用从 iPad
iPad.
分享的功能
We can't have a student copying
我们不能允许学生
all the questions and using the
复制所有的问题
Share menu to ship them off to
使用“分享”菜单
another iPad of another student
将它们传到外界其他学生的
outside.
iPad 上
We need to turn off that
我们也需要关闭
universal clipboard as well.
通用剪贴板
In fact, we need to turn off a
实际上
whole lot of things.
我们需要关闭很多东西
You really do need to turn off
为了进行安全严格的考试
all these features like this to
你确实需要
run a safe and secure test.
关闭这些功能
This combination of locking iOS,
锁定 iOS
as I showed you before, plus
像我之前展示的那样
automatically disabling all
再加上自动禁用
these features is called
所有需要禁用的功能
automatic assessment
就叫做
configuration.
自主评价配置
Now AAC, automatic assessment
现在 AAC 也就是
way I showed you with ASAM.
与刚才所示的 ASAM 大致相同
It's the exact same function.
需要使用同一个函数
You call a function true to
你给函数传值 true 就是锁定
lock, false to unlock.
传值 false 就是解锁
You check the status.
你可以检查状态
Exactly the same process right
与刚刚的过程
there.
一模一样
But in addition, the moment you
但除此之外
lock with this function, all
在你使用该函数锁定的同时
these features are going to be
所有列出的功能
automatically disabled for the
也会在考试期间
duration of your test, and when
被自动禁用
you call the unlock function,
当你调用解锁函数时
they're all enabled.
这些功能又被启用
There is a requirement here.
它需要满足一个条件
This works on any iPad, whether
虽然这项技术在任何 iPad 上均可运行
it's managed or not, but it's a
无论它是否被管理
pretty powerful technique, so
但因为这项技术非常强大
you need to have a special
在请求被成功处理之前
entitlement in your application
你的应用
before that request will
必须获得
succeed.
特殊权限
Technically, the request is
技术上来说
called com.apple.developer.
这项请求叫做
edu-assessment-mode.
com.apple.developer.edu-assessment-mode.
You need to apply to Apple for
你需要向 Apple
this entitlement, and once you
申请这项权限
have it, your application will
一旦获得
be able to lock and unlock with
你的 App 就可以锁定和解锁
no need for a supervised device
不需要使用被监控的设备
and no need for white listing.
也不需要被加入白名单了
Your app needs to be built with
在构建你的 App 时
a profile that includes this
你需要包含一份含有此特殊权限的
special entitlement.
配置文件
And once it locks, well, how
那么一旦锁定了 iPad
does it unlock?
要如何解锁呢？
Well, the device is locked.
现在这台设备被锁定了
Normally, it would unlock,
通常情况下它会在
because at the end of the test,
考试结束时被解锁
you would call the function that
因为你将调用函数并传值 false
says false, time to end our
考试时间到了
session, the student has
学生们
submitted the answers.
必须提交答案
But the iPad also unlocks if the
但当用户重启 iPad 时
user reboots it.
它也会被解锁
This isn't like single app mode
这不像单一 App 模式
where we permanently keep you in
可以永久的
a device.
锁定一台设备
It's a temporary single app
这只是暂时的
mode.
单一 App 模式
And it also unlocks after eight
八个小时之后
hours.
它也会被解锁
This is a -- if you are
如果你管理的是
administering a particular long
一场非常长的考试
test, you might want to be aware
你可能需要留意
of this.
这一点
You will get a notification that
当锁定状态改变时
the locked status has changed,
你会收到通知
and you could take that
并且你将有机会
opportunity to lock it again.
再次锁定
Let me know if you're creating a
如果你创建了一个
test that takes eight hours to
需要八个小时才能完成的考试
finish.
请告诉我
I do not want to write that
我是不想参加
particular test.
那种考试的
But what people see when they're
使用这一技术时
doing this is this.
人们看到的是这个界面
This is a sample application.
这是一个简单的应用
There's sample code associated
你也可以下载
with this session that you can
与本场会议相关的
download.
简单代码
Two buttons that turn locking on
这两个按钮控制
and off.
锁定和解锁
This app was built with the
这个 App 是获得正确权限后
right entitlement, and there's a
构建的
text field where you can try
这里有一个文本框
typing to see if spellchecking
你可以通过输入
works, and there's a log of what
查看拼写检查能否运行
happens.
所有操作都会被记录在日志中
When you tap the Enable App Lock
当你点击这里的“开启 App 锁定”
here and call that function I've
调用我刚刚所说的
been talking about, this panel
函数
is automatically displayed.
这个面板就会自动出现
The gives the user the
它让用户有机会
opportunity to say yes or no,
选择是否
they are willing to enter the
愿意进入
lock session.
锁定会话
And if they tap yes, a banner
如果他们点击“是”
automatically appears at the top
一条横幅会自动出现在顶端
that says your iPad is now
显示“你的 iPad 已被锁定
locked, and it's going to unlock
当你完成考试
after eight hours or when you
或八小时后
finish the test, and then that
会解锁”
goes away after five seconds.
五秒之后该横幅消失
Now the iPad is locked until
现在 iPad 就被锁定了
such time as somebody runs,
直到有人运行
calls the function to unlock.
或调用解锁函数
In this demo app, tapping the
在这个 demo App 中
red button calls the unlock
点击红色按钮即为调用解锁函数
function, then you get another
接着另一条横幅
banner across the top.
会出现在顶端
"Your iPad is no longer locked."
“你的 iPad 已解锁“
In between the green and the
在点击绿色按钮后红色按钮前
red, the Home button was
Home 键
successful disabled, and this is
被成功禁用
a pretty simple sample
这只是一个非常简单的
application.
应用
Just two buttons with two action
只有两个按钮
methods.
和两个动作方法
One calls the function with true
一个调用函数传值 true
to lock.
进行锁定
The other one says false to
另一个传值 false
unlock.
进行解锁
Let's talk about some of the
让我们讨论一下
considerations in here.
这里要关注的问题
It's pretty good that the apps
App 能够自行锁定和解锁
can lock and unlock themselves,
是非常好的
and it's great for assessment,
对评价考试而言
that all these other features,
在锁定的同时
like spell check, are
能够自动禁用其他一些功能
automatically turned off in
如拼写检查
addition to the locking.
也非常理想
You, the developer, have
你作为开发人员
control, and this doesn't
可以进行控制
require a managed device.
并且不需要被管理的设备
In a school situation, this will
如果是在学校
work on a device the student
学生从家里带来的设备
brings from home.
也可以运行
However, you do need this
然而你的应用
particular app entitlement in
还是需要特定的 App 权限
your application, and this
该权限也只对
entitlement is only for
评价开发人员
assessment developers.
开放
How would you implement this in
那么要如何在 App 中
your app?
实现该功能
Well, the first step is to
嗯 首先是要
actually apply to Apple for this
向 Apple 申请
entitlement, which will be
这一权限
granted to assessment developers
该权限只对评价开发人员
but not to anybody else, and
开放
then you build a provisioning
然后你需要构建
profile that includes that
一个配置文件
entitlement, and build your app
其中包括该权限
with that profile.
并使用配置文件构建你的 App
The way you ask for this
申请该项权限的方法
entitlement is to submit a tech
是提交一份
support incident, and tell us,
技术支持申请
tell Apple that you would like
告诉 Apple
the education assessment mode
你需要教育评价模式的
entitlement.
权限
And then once that's been
一旦被授予该权限
granted to you, you can go to
你就可以
the developer portal and build a
前往开发人员门户网站
new profile that includes that
构建包括该项授权的
entitlement.
新配置文件
You will only see this selection
只有获得授权
here if you've been granted the
你才可以在这里看到该选项
entitlement, and you can now
你现在就可以
build a provisioning profile
构建
that has this special
包含特殊权限的
entitlement in it.
配置文件了
Don't forget this step.
别忘了这一步
It's not enough for Apple to
Apple 给予你
grant you the entitlement.
授权还是不够的
You have to create a profile
你需要创建嵌入该授权的
that has it embedded, and
配置文件
download it, and use it in
并且下载下来
Xcode.
用到 Xcode 中
Also, don't forget that you want
还有 别忘了
to apply this to several
你需要将该项授权
different profiles.
添加到几份不同的配置文件中
It's not enough just to put the
仅仅将授权添加到
entitlement in your development
开发配置文件中
profile.
是不够的
You should put it in the
你还应该将它添加到
distribution one, and if you've
分发配置文件中
done it correctly, you should
如果操作正确
see here in Xcode, once you
你可以在 Xcode 中看到这个
select a profile with this
当你选择了包含授权的配置文件时
entitlement in it, you can touch
你可以点击
that little info button, and you
小小的信息按钮
can see the entitlements that
查看嵌入的
are built in here.
权限
That's the way to confirm that
这就是确认
you're doing this right.
操作是否正确的方法
If you see that magic string
如果你可以在这里看到这行神奇的字符
there, com.apple.developer.
com.apple.developer.edu-assessment-mode
edu-assessment-mode, you're good
那你的操作
to go.
就是正确的
You can now build an application
现在你可以真正
that actually uses this
使用这项技术
technology.
构建应用了
When would you do it?
那么何时才能使用呢
Well, when you're ready to enter
当你准备好进入考试时
the test, you'd call the magic
请调用函数并传值 true
function with true, and when
当你准备
you're ready to get out of the
退出考试时
test, you'd call it with false,
调用并传值 false
and it's very important to check
检查它是否成功运行
whether it worked or not,
是非常重要的
because there were some
因为在有些情况下
scenarios where it can fail.
它可能会失败
I'm going to try actually doing
我要试着
this.
完成该功能
I'm going to try actually
我要试着构建一些
building something that they
今年
used this year.
在使用的东西
Take my life in my hands here.
我很紧张
So you remember this testing
你应该还记得
application that I showed you
之前我向你们展示的
before.
考试应用
I have a secure version and an
这台 iPad 上
insecure version of it on this
有这个考试应用的
iPad.
安全版本和不安全版本
I'm going to show you the
我将向你们展示
insecure version, just to
不安全版本
highlight some of the problems
仅仅是用来强调
that might come up in a test,
考试中可能发生的问题
then I'm going to change the
然后我会将不安全版本
insecure version into the secure
变成
version.
安全版本
This is the insecure version of
这是考试的
the test.
不安全版本
If I touch Start Test, I could
如果我点击“开始考试”
do all kinds of cheating things.
我可以用一切方法作弊
I could look up Canada in the
我可以在内置词典中
built-in dictionary.
查询“加拿大”
Oh, there's the capitol right
哦 首都
there.
就在这里
It's Ottawa.
是“渥太华”
That's pretty good.
很好
Let's assume that we've blocked
让我们假设
the Home button.
Home 键已经被禁用了
Even if we've blocked the Home
就算禁用了
button, a lot of other stuff is
Home 键
possible.
我们还可以做很多其他的事情
If I type my answer up here,
如果我在这里输入我的答案
O-T-T, I'm getting suggestions
O-T-T
in the completion bar that
在补全栏的提示中
happen to include the correct
刚好就包括
answer.
正确答案
You'd probably like to disable
你可能也想在考试中
that in a test as well.
禁用该功能
You should probably disable the
你可能也应该禁用
share sheet.
分享表单
We do not want students sending
我们不希望学生
the questions to their friends
把问题发给
somewhere else.
其他地方的朋友
All this stuff needs to be
这些功能应该
disabled in addition to the Home
被一并禁用
button.
除了禁用 Home 键之外
I mean, my Home button's still
我的意思是
working here.
现在我还能用 Home 键
That's the first problem.
这就是第一个问题
So I'm going to show you the
所以我将向你们展示
code for this particular
这个特定应用的
application here, and then we're
代码
going to try turning this into a
然后我们将试着把它
secure version.
改为安全版本
So this is really a "nothing
这个 App 真的
app."
什么都没有
I put no effort into this
我就是
application at all.
随手一写
It's a couple of view
这里有一些
controllers, and we touch the
视图控制器
Start the Test button, and it
当我们点击“开始考试”按钮时
loads another view controller
就会载入这里的一个其他的
right here.
视图控制器
That's the time that we want to
现在我们
turn locking on.
想要锁定它
There are, however, a few
然而
prerequisites that you have to
你还要完成一些
do before you can do this
先决条件
locking dance.
才能开始锁定
First of all, you have to have a
首先你必须有
provisioning profile with the
包含正确权限的
right entitlement in it.
配置文件
You have to have applied to
你必须向
Apple for this entitlement, and
Apple 申请该权限
generated a provision profile
并且生成
that includes it.
包含它的配置文件
I fortunately have done that, so
我刚好已经完成了
I'm just going to change my code
所以我只需要
signing right here to use this
在这里更改我的代码签名
provisioning profile, which I
使用这个配置文件
have previously downloaded, and
这是我之前下载的
it has the magic entitlement in
它包含神奇的
it.
权限
I can verify that touching the
我可以通过点击这里的
info button right here, and
信息按钮验证
you'll see that the
你可以看到
com.apple.developer.
com.apple.developer.edu-assessment-mode entitlement
edu-assessment-mode entitlement
已经被嵌入
is buried in here.
这里
We're good.
非常好
I can compile an app now that
现在我可以使用
will use this particular
这个特殊的权限
entitlement.
编译 App 了
That's step one.
这是第一步
Step two is that Xcode these
第二步是
days is particularly cautious,
因为最近 Xcode 变得非常严谨
I'll say, and Xcode wants you to
需要你
state exactly which entitlement
创建权限文件
this app needs to use right now
声明该 App 现在
by creating an entitlements
需要使用的
file.
到底是哪个权限
It's not enough just to have the
拥有包含权限的
provisioning profile with the
配置文件
entitlement in it.
还不够
You also need an actual
你还需要一个
entitlements file.
真正的权限文件
I've made one of these here.
我已经写了一个
Entitlements files are just keys
权限文件就是这样的
and values like that.
Key 和值
So I'm going to add this.
所以我将添加该文件
This is the awkward part of the
这就是这个 demo
demo.
比较尴尬的部分
I'm going to add this
我将
entitlements file to my project,
权限文件添加到我的工程文件中
and I'm going to go to the build
然后前往构建设置
settings, my favorite part of
Xcode 中我最喜欢的部分
Xcode, looking around at the
查看权限的
build settings for the
构建设置
entitlements, and I'm going to
并且告诉 Xcode
tell it that I want to use that
我想要使用那个文件
file, AAC.entitlements.
AAC.entitlements
I'm specifying that that's my
我明确说明了
entitlements file specifying
我的权限文件明确说明了
that, yes, I really do want to
是的我确实想用
use education assessment.
教育评价
All right.
好的
Now I think we're okay to go.
我想一切顺利
This is still an insecure test,
但它仍然是一个不安全的考试
because it's not making any
因为没有调用
effort to call the locking
锁定函数
function, so I'm going to put
我要将这部分
that in.
加进来
I'm going to put a lock around
我要在现有的这行
this present line right here.
周围添加锁定
Here we go.
好的
[inaudible] Apple we have these
在 Apple
little shortcuts ready to go.
我们有一些捷径
This is the block of code that I
这是我刚刚复制进去的
just pasted in.
代码块
We're going to request a Guided
我们需要请求 UIAccessibilityRequestGuidedAccessSession()
Access session with the
并且将参数
parameter true.
赋值为 true
True means lock, yes, now.
True 就是锁定
And if it succeeds, we're going
现在如果成功锁定了
to do one thing.
我们要做一件事
If it fails, we're going to do
如果失败
another thing.
我们要做另外的事情
So I'm going to move this line
所以我要把这行代码
of code up into that if block up
移进这里的
there.
if 代码块
By the way, if you take nothing
顺便说一句
else home from this session,
如果你在这节会议中没有学到其他东西
command option left bracket
至少要记住 command+option+(
moves lines of code up, and
可以上移代码行
command option right bracket
command+option+）
moves them down.
可以下移代码行
This is the greatest thing.
这很重要
Hey, oh, look at that fun.
看看 多有趣
Anyway, we is now put that
总之
inside this if statement.
现在我们把代码移进了 if 语句
So we're going to request a
所以我们要请求锁定
lock, and if it succeeded ,
如果成功
we're going to present the other
将显示另一个
view controller.
视图控制器
It's important to pair the locks
有锁定就要有解锁
with the unlocks.
这很重要
You have to have some way of
有很多方式可以
unlocking the application.
解锁应用
And in this particularly
在这个
extremely simple app , I'm just
极其简单的 App 中
going to do it here.
我是这么做的
Every time this main test picker
每一次考试选择主视图
view shows up on the screen,
出现在屏幕上时
we're going to unlock.
我们都将进行解锁
This is an unlock call to that
这是对该函数的
function.
解锁调用
We're passing it false to say
将 false 传递给函数
please try to unlock the device.
意味着请求函数尝试解锁设备
So we lock the device when we
所以当我们离开考试选择界面时
leave the test picker screen,
会锁定设备
and we unlock it when we come
当我们回到考试选择界面时
back to the test picker screen.
又会解锁
I think we're okay here.
我想没有问题了
Let's find out.
让我们看看结果
Try running this.
尝试运行一下
And here it is.
有了
So I'm going to choose the
所以我将选择
geography test, and I'm going to
地理考试
touch Start Test.
并点击“开始考试”
That's when the lock code is
这时锁定代码
invoked.
被调用
I'll touch Start Test.
点击“开始考试”
now it's asking me.
现在它在询问我
Now it's asking me the user to
询问我用户是否
confirm that we like to enter
确认愿意进入
single app mode for the duration
单一 App 模式
of eight hours or until the test
直到八小时以后或考试结束
is over, and I'll say yes.
我选择“是”
Now that I'm in the geography
现在我在地理考试中
test, you'll see the banner at
你可以看到顶端的横幅
the top advising me that would
提示我锁定将
like for the next eight hours or
在未来的八个小时持续
until the test is over.
或在考试结束时解锁
I can't look anything up here
我再也不能在这里
anymore.
查看任何东西了
That had the look up button on
这里原先有
it before.
“查找”按钮的
I could have looked up the
我本来可以在
answer in Wikipedia, but that's
Wikipedia 中查找答案
been automatically turned off.
但它已经被自动关闭了
My spell checking has been
我的拼写检查
automatically turned off down
也在这里被
here.
自动关闭了
we're really taking all the fun
在考试期间
things out of the iPad here for
我们禁用了 iPad
the duration of this test here,
一切有趣的功能
just to ensure that we have a
只是为了确保
test with some integrity here.
有一场公平公正的考试
The capital of Canada is Ottawa.
加拿大的首都是渥太华
Alright. And when I touch the
很好
Submit button, we return to this
当我点击“提交”按钮
screen, and ASAM is turned off
回到该界面
with the other function I put
ASAM 以及我设定其他功能
in.
就被关闭了
now the Home button is now
现在 Home 键
working.
可以使用
So the Home button was not
在考试时
working while we were in the
Home 键则
test.
不可使用
All those cheating services were
所有可供作弊的服务
not working either, and once we
都无法使用
exited the test, everything was
直到我们退出考试
fine.
一切又恢复原状
I'm feeling kind of confident
我现在感觉
here.
很有信心
I want to try another test.
我想试试另一个考试
I think I did okay in the
我觉得我在地理考试中
geography test.
表现不错
Let's try another one here.
让我们试试另一个
Spelling. I'm good at spelling.
拼写 我拼写很好
So we'll lock as we go into the
所以当我们进入拼写考试时
spelling test.
就锁定住了
Here are my spelling words.
这是我要拼写的单词
What's that?
它是什么
&gt;&gt; Schnauzer.
&gt;&gt; Schnauzer
&gt;&gt; Schnauzer, okay.
&gt;&gt; Schnauzer 好的
Can I have the definition of
我能知道“schnauzer”的
"schnauzer"?
定义吗
&gt;&gt; A medium or small-sized dog
&gt;&gt; 中小体型的
of a German breed with a closed
德国犬
wiry coat and heavy whiskers
毛发浓密硬直
around the muzzle.
口鼻处有浓密的胡须
&gt;&gt; Okay, I think I can spell
&gt;&gt; 好的我想我可以拼写
that.
这个单词
Can I have it in a sentence,
我能知道
please?
这个单词的例句吗
&gt;&gt; Get a load of that guy's
&gt;&gt; 仔细看那个家伙的
schnauzer.
schnauzer
&gt;&gt; All right, schnauzer.
&gt;&gt; 好的 schnauzer
Let's see here.
让我看看
[laughter].
笑声
&gt;&gt; S-C-H-N-A-U.
&gt;&gt; S-C-H-N-A-U.
&gt;&gt; You notice I'm not getting
&gt;&gt; 你应该注意到
any typing situations here.
我没有得到任何输入建议
&gt;&gt; Zed.
&gt;&gt; Z
&gt;&gt; Zed, thank you.
&gt;&gt; Z 谢谢
From Canada.
要拼完了
&gt;&gt; E-R. [ringing].
&gt;&gt; E-R. 铃声
&gt;&gt; Hey, all right.
&gt;&gt; 哇好了
I got that one right.
我拼对了一个
I'm feeling kind of cocky.
现在我有点小骄傲了
I want to try another word.
我想再试一个单词
I got ten minutes left.
我还有十分钟
I'll do a couple more words in
我可以在拼写考试中
the spelling test.
再做几个单词
What do you say?
你们觉得呢
Let's try one more word in the
让我们在拼写考试中
spelling test.
再试一个单词
&gt;&gt; Syzygy.
&gt;&gt; Syzygy
&gt;&gt; Uh-oh. What?
&gt;&gt; 呃哦 什么
&gt;&gt; Can I have the definition.
&gt;&gt; 请告诉我定义
&gt;&gt; A conjunction or opposition.
&gt;&gt;一种汇合或对立
&gt;&gt; That's not really helping me.
&gt;&gt; 这没什么帮助
&gt;&gt; Syzygy.
&gt;&gt; Syzygy.
&gt;&gt; Can you use it in a sentence.
&gt;&gt; 请给我一个例句
&gt;&gt; Your spelling bee word is
&gt;&gt; 你需要拼写的单词是
"syzygy."
“syzygy”
&gt;&gt; Okay. Man, I don't know.
&gt;&gt; 好吧 天哪我不知道
&gt;&gt; S-Y-Z-Y-G-Y.
&gt;&gt; S-Y-Z-Y-G-Y.
[ Ringing ]
铃声
.
&gt;&gt; 嘿好的
One more, one more.
再做一个 再做一个
I'm feeling pretty good here.
我感觉很好
Let's try one here.
让我们试试这个
&gt;&gt; Calfafa [phonetic].
&gt;&gt; Covfefe
&gt;&gt; What's that again?
&gt;&gt; 再读一遍
[ Applause ]
掌声
.
Colfafa
&gt;&gt; Jeez, I don't know that one.
&gt;&gt; 天哪 这个我不知道
Can you use it in a sentence?
能给我一个例句吗
&gt;&gt; Despite the constant negative
&gt;&gt; 尽管出现了持续的负面
press, calfafa.
新闻报道 covfefe
&gt;&gt; Calfafa.
&gt;&gt;
All right.
好吧
C-O-U--
C-O-U--
[ Ringing ]
铃声
.
.
Oh, I was spelling it the
哦 我在用加拿大的方法
Canadian way, C-O-U.
拼写 C-O-U.
I'm sorry.
不好意思
Anyway, I can't hit the Home
总之在考试进行时
button while this test is going
我不能点击 Home 键
on, because we requested a
因为我们请求了
locked session.
锁定会话
The moment I hit Submit, I'll
我点击“提交”的时候
transition back to that other
会转回另一个界面
screen, and I'm now able to hit
现在就能点击 Home 键了
the Home button as the test is
因为考试已经
over.
结束
So it's that straightforward.
所以非常简单
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
.
谢谢
Oh, you're too kind.
你们太好了
So it's pretty straightforward
所以一旦你获得权限
to actually add this to your
将它添加到
application once you have that
你的应用
entitlement.
是非常简单的
I've got to remind you.
我要提醒你
You've got to get that
你需要从 Apple
entitlement from Apple before
获得权限
the locking and the disabling is
才能进行
going to work.
锁定和禁用
Let's talk about a couple of
让我们讨论一些
other considerations.
其他问题
I've mentioned that the request
我提过
to lock might fail, and that's
锁定请求可能会失败
true in the ASAM model where
这在 ASAM 模型中可能会发生
you're deploying to a supervised
你在受监控的设备上使用该模型
device and also the AAC model
在 AAC 模型中也可能发生
where you're deploying to any
在获得权限的情况下
device with the entitlement.
你可以在任意设备上使用该模型
The request to lock can fail, so
锁定的请求可能会失败
you really do need to check that
所以你的确应该检查
parameter.
参数
In ASAM, it will fail if the
在 ASAM 中请求可能会因为
device is not supervised and if
设备没有被监控
the bundle identifier hasn't
数据包标识符没有正确设置
been set up properly.
而失败
In other words, if the device is
换句话说
not being managed properly for
如果设备没有针对考试进行正确管理
your test, an ASAM request will
ASAM 请求
fail.
将会失败
In AAC, it will fail if your app
在 AAC 中请求可能会因为
does not have this entitlement
你的 App 没有嵌入权限
built in.
而失败
In both cases, it will fail if
而在这两种情况下
the user hit "no" on that button
如果用户在
where -- that panel where
被询问是否想要锁定的面板上
they're asked if they want to
点击了“否”按钮
lock or not.
请求都会失败
But, and this is kind of weird,
但是有点奇怪的是
it will fail if the device is
如果设备已经被锁定
already locked.
请求还是会失败
This is a little weird.
这个有点奇怪
If you make the lock request
如果你连续进行了两次
twice in a row, the first one
锁定请求
will succeed.
第一次会成功
You'll be locked.
设备被锁定
If you ask to lock again, the
如果你再次要求锁定
second one will fail, but you'll
第二次请求会失败
still be locked.
但你的设备还是在锁定状态
So you have to be careful about
所以你在设置
this in the setup of an
评价考试应用时
assessment application.
要格外小心
All those restrictions of
包括禁用
disabling the dictionary and
字典和
spell checking, those are only
拼写检查在内的所有限制
there if it was your app that
只有当你的 App
actually successfully called
成功调用
that
UIRequestGuidedAccessSession()
UIRequestGuidedAccessSession
函数时
function.
才会生效
If you were locked for some
如果你的设备因为
other reason, those restrictions
其他原因被锁定
are not going to be in place.
这些限制将不会生效
So it is a good practice to
所以进行检查
check.
是良策
Before you try to lock the
在尝试锁定设备之前
device, check if it's already
检查它是否
locked.
已经被锁定
Because if it already is locked,
因为如果它已经被锁定
and you didn't do it, something
并且不是你做的
is wrong.
将会发生一些问题
We're in an odd situation.
这个场景很奇怪
Maybe somebody walked up and
可能有人走了过来
turned on Guided Access with the
点击三次 Home 键
triple tap thing.
开启了“引导式访问”
If they did that, the
如果他们这么做了
restrictions are not going to be
限制条件将无法
disabled properly.
正确生效
So it's important that you
因此进行检查
actually check.
是非常重要的
Here's one way.
这里是一种方法
You can check when the app is
你可以在 App 启动时
launched.
进行检查
We suggest you wait for two
我们建议你在 App 启动后
seconds after app launch,
等待两秒
because it takes a moment to
因为锁定所有东西
lock everything, but you can
需要花费一定时间
check after app launch, call
但你可以在 App 启动后检查
that Is GuidedAccessEnabled
使用 UIAccessibilityIsGuidedAccessEnabled()
function.
函数
And if you are locked
如果你在启动后
immediately after launch,
立即锁定
something is wrong in your
你的考试环境
testing environment.
会出现一些问题
You weren't supposed to be
你不应该
locked at this point.
立即锁定
For a test, you should stop at
你应该在此时立即
that point.
停止考试
You should not proceed with the
不要继续进行
test.
考试
Similarly, you should do a test
同样的
before attempting to call the
在试图调用锁定函数前
lock function.
你也需要进行考试
You should check that Guided
你应该检查
Access is false,
UIAccessibilityIsGuidedAccessEnabled()
GuidedAccessEnabled is false
的值为 false
before you try to lock.
然后再试图锁定
You want to make sure you're in
你需要确认
the right state before you call
在调用锁定函数之前的
the locking the function to
状态是正确的
ensure that not only is the
这也不仅能够
device locked, but it's locked
锁定设备
with the restrictions.
还能让限制条件生效
Here's another consideration for
标准化考试
a standardized test.
还有一个需要考虑的问题
Probably a good idea to clear
可能在考试开始前后
the paste board coming in and
清理粘贴板
leaving your test.
是一个好主意
AAC automatically disables the
AAC 会自动禁用
universal clipboard for sharing
用于分享到其他设备的
to other devices, but you need
通用剪贴板
to clear the built-in system
但你需要在考试开始时
paste board when the test starts
清理系统内置的粘贴板
to keep a child from copying the
这样孩子就不能复制笔记中的内容
test in notes and then launching
再启动
the app.
App 了
You want to clear that out.
你也需要清理粘贴出来的内容
You probably want to clear it on
你可能希望
exit of the test as well, so
在退出考试时一并清理
they don't copy the questions
这样学生就无法拷贝题目
and see it somewhere else.
在其他地方查看了
Pretty straightforward to do
要实现
that.
非常简单
You just set the items of the
你只需要将
general paste board to an empty
通用粘贴板中的项目
array.
指向空数组
You should probably consider
你可能也会考虑
disabling third party keyboards
在评价考试 App 中
in an assessment app as well.
禁用第三方键盘
Third party keyboards are app
第三方键盘是
extensions, and they're not
App 扩展
blocked by AAC.
且并不会被 AAC 屏蔽
You might have an application
你可能会有类似这样的应用
like this, where the student has
学生会安装
installed another keyboard which
其他的键盘
actually some keyboards actually
有一些键盘确实
support searching right in the
在键盘内提供
keyboard.
搜索功能
You could search for the capital
你可以在键盘里
of Canada right there in the
搜索加拿大的首都
keyboard and get the answer.
并且得到答案
That's probably not a good
这不是一个适合考试
keyboard to use in a test.
使用的键盘
So as a developer of an
作为评价测试应用的
assessment application, you can
开发人员
implement this function in your
你可以在应用委托中
application delegate to allow or
实现这一功能
disallow specific types of
根据需要
extensions as they are being
允许使用或禁用
voted.
特定的扩展
I would suggest just disallowing
我建议最好
all of them, especially
全部禁用
keyboards.
特别是键盘
But disallow all extensions in a
在标准化考试 App 中禁用
standardized test app.
所有扩展
Remember, the goal is to take
记住 目的是
all the fun out of the iPad for
在考试期间
the duration of the test, and
移除 iPad 的所有乐趣功能
then restore the fun when we're
但在考试结束之后
done.
还是要恢复这些乐趣功能
Let me just review again the
让我再次复习
difference between these two
两种技术的区别
techniques, because in software,
因为在软件上
they're exactly the same.
它们几乎是一样的
You call this same function,
你要调用相同的函数
UIAccessibilityRequest
UIAccessibilityRequestGuidedAccessSession()
GuidedAccessSession, and the
但是效果是
effect is different, depending
不同的
on how the devices and your app
取决于你的设备和 App
are set up.
是如何设置的
The code is the same.
代码相同
You call that function.
你要调用该函数
In each scenario, the device is
在每个场景中
locked.
设备都被锁定了
Remember though that in ASAM we
记住尽管在 ASAM 中
have to be dealing with a
我们必须使用
managed and supervised device.
受到管理和监控的设备
In AAC, we can deal with any
在 AAC 中 我们可以使用
device, so long as your app has
任何设备
the entitlement.
只要你的 App 拥有权限
But the biggest difference is
但最大的区别在于
that AAC also turns off a whole
AAC 在锁定会话期间
bunch of other stuff for the
也锁定了
duration of the locking session.
很多其他功能
So that is the technology you
所以这是
want to use if you're an
作为评价系统开发人员
assessment developer, to lock an
想要使用的技术
application.
锁定应用
Other developers may find that
其他开发人员会发现
ASAM meets their needs, but AAC
ASAM 满足他们的需求
is specifically for assessment
但 AAC 是为评价系统开发人员
developers.
特制的
So we talked about four ways to
我们讨论了锁定 App 的
lock an app.
四种方法
Guided Access, lots of fun.
“引导式访问”非常有趣
Do that when you get home.
可以在家中使用
Lock your children into the
将你的孩子锁在
SpongeBob Squarepants
海绵宝宝应用中
application so that they can't
这样他们就不会
look at your mail, and then
看你的邮件
that's a nice easy end user sort
对用户来说
of thing to do.
操作非常简单
Works on any device with any
适用于任何设备的
app.
任何 App
Single app mode is good for
单一 App 模式适合自助服务
kiosks, but it requires the
但需要管理员
administrator to push out a
推送命令
command to a fleet of managed
到一系列
supervised devices, and then
受管理的设备上
they are pretty much permanently
然后它们就会被
locked to the application.
几乎永久的所锁在某个应用里
And then ASAM and AAC are the
ASAM 和 AAC 的
same software function with two
软件函数相同
different effects, depending on
但效果不同
the setup.
取决于设置
Two different effects depending
不同的效果取决于
on whether your app has this
你的 App 是否有权限
entitlement and whether the
和设备
devices are managed or not.
是否受管理
So there's a bunch of related
因此本节会议
sessions at the conference.
有很多相关会议
I hope you enjoyed all the
我希望你们喜欢
related sessions.
所有的相关会议中
I like that second one on
我喜欢第二个
heifers and HVAC.
介绍 HEIF 和 HVAC 的
I think that's the air
我觉得那节会议
conditioning for cows.
很不错
Oh, I'm reading that wrong.
哦我读错了
HEIF and HEVC.
HEIF 和 HEVC
A lot of our assessment
我们有很多评价考试开发人员
developers deliver web content
将交付网络内容
as part of their applications,
作为应用的一部分
so I think these are
因此我认为
particularly relevant sessions
对使用的人来说
for people to use.
这些是特别相关的会议
But for more information and for
要了解更多信息
-- including a sample
包括一个
application that demonstrates
展示实现过程的
how all this works, please take
样例应用
a look at the website here for
请查看
Session 760.
会议 716 的网站
Thank you very much.
非常感谢
Thank you for coming.
谢谢大家的到来
I hope you enjoy the week.
希望你们本周过得愉快
[ Applause ]
掌声